Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; 1; 4367
  - School of Business, 2008 October 16-2015 September 11; 1.10; 438
    - Business: 5/11/04 @ 10:30 AM CC Small Fountain area group photo; MBA Grads digital, 2004 May 5; 12.6 MB 10
    - Business: 5/11/04 @ 10:30 AM CC Small Fountain area group photo; MBA Grads digital, 2004 May 5; 12.6 MB 10
    - President: 4/28/04 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President Ryan's Speech to Faculty digital, 2004 May 13; 55.2 MB 53
    - Business: 5/4/04 @ Noon BA-233 MBA Presentations / group shot (Sanjay Goel's class) digital, 2004 May 13; 10.6 MB 8
    - Business: 2/3/05 @ 5 PM NYC School of Business Event digital, 2005 February 7; 243.3 MB 187
    - Business: 2/11/05 @ 10:50 AM BA 229 Finance Dept Faculty digital, 2005 February 18; 21.3 MB 13
    - Media and Marketing: 2/4/05 @ 3 PM CC west lounge Student Association greets President Hall digital, 2005 February 18; 99.4 MB 65
    - Media and Marketing: 2/5/05 @ 1 PM RACC Hall of Fame Room Executive Board greets President Hall digital, 2005 February 21; 106.2 MB 45
    - Business: 4/6/05 @ 11:30 AM BA 220 plaque unveiling digital, 2005 April 12; 31.2 MB 25
    - Business: 5/4/05 @ 11:30 AM School of Business Awards Luncheon digital, 2005 April 21; 124.3 MB 85
    - Business: 5/4/05 @ 6:30 PM CESTM MBA Research Forum digital, 2005 April 21; 54.6 MB 18
    - Media and Marketing: 4/9/05 @ 10 AM Draper 113 Pres Hall meets College of Info Science digital, 2005 April 22; 32.9 MB 25
    - Media and Marketing: 4/11/05 @ 10:30 AM IT Services IT Suite LC Pres Hall tours IT Services digital, 2005 April 25; 46.7 MB 27
    - Media and Marketing: 4/11/05 @ noon Prez Rez Pine Hills Neighborhood Assoc. Lunch digital, 2005 April 25; 26.3 MB 14
    - Business: 5/11/05 @ 10 AM CC Assembly Hall MBA class photo digital, 2005 May 4; 21.5 MB 13
    - Business: 10/20/05 @ 5:30 - 7:30 PM Albany Marriott Wolf Rd. Business Alumni Networking event digital, 2005 August 5; 215.7 MB 141
    - Media and Marketing: 9/15/05 @ 5:45 PM SS-131 Marketing Class w/ FBI client liaison digital, 2005 September 23; 65.2 MB 46
    - President: 10/11/05 @ 10:30 AM Standish Room Check Presentation / School of Business digital, 2005 October 25; 45.4 MB 19
    - Special Events: 10/17/05 @ 11 am Standish Room Norm Snyder gift announcement / School of Business\ digital, 2005 October 31; 76.3 MB 31
    - President: 10/17/05 @ Noon NYS Assembly Bldg Pres Hall and Hearing for Higher Education digital, 2005 November 1; 116.9 MB 68
    - Business: 11/10/05 @ 5:30 PM - 7:30 PM UBS Investment Bank / 299 Park Ave (27th Fl. Corner of Park and 49th St. NYC Women's Networking Reception NYC digital, 2005 November 17; 1.0 GB 152
    - UAF: 12/9/05 @ 7:30 AM Ft. Orange Club Albany School of Business: Vision for the Future digital, 2005 November 29; 134.9 MB 46
    - Media and Marketing: 2/4/06 @ 5 PM RACC Big Purple Growl and Ferocious Feast, 2006 February 20; 225.8 MB 247
    - Media and Marketing: 2/15/06 @ 1:30 PM BA- HR Lab 2nd Fl Prof. Hal Guetal and students, 2006 February 28; 107.3 MB 51
    - Business: 3/1/06 @ Noon Standish Room Hugh Johnson / First Albany Corp, 2006 March 2; 92.5 MB 48
    - Business School: 5/10/06 @ 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM location TBA SofB Awards Ceremony, 2006 May 11; 179.1 MB 83
    - Business School: 5/10/06 @ 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM location TBA SofB Awards Ceremony, 2006 May 11; 179.6 MB 83
    - Business: 5/10/06 @ 6 - 7:30 PM CESTM Rotunda Research Forum, 2006 May 18; 8.2 MB 4
    - Business: 5/17/06 @ 10:15 AM CC Ballroom Global Class Picture, 2006 May 18; 25.0 MB 11
    - Business: 5/17/06 @ 10:15 AM CC Ballroom Global Class Picture, 2006 May 18; 45.9 MB 13
    - Business: 5/10/06 @ 6 - 7:30 PM CESTM Rotunda Research Forum, 2006 May 18; 130.2 MB 80
    - School of Business: 11/2/06 from 5:30 - 7:30, Albany Marriott for School of Business Alumni Reception., 2006 November 2; 255.1 MB 121
    - Development: 11/20/06 @ 3:30 PM School of Business for photo of Dean Paul Leonard, 2006 November 20; 109.1 MB 55
    - 12/18/06 @ 10:00 a.m. in BA 364 (Dean Leonard's office) for photo of Albina Grignon and Dean Leonard, awarding a School of Business student a gift, for our Connections newsletter., 2006 December 19; 6.4 MB 8
    - School of Business: 2/16/07 @ 1 - 2 PM BA 313A for two group shots., 2007 February 16; 286.2 MB 214
    - School of Business: 3/01/07 @ 10 AM Dean's Office School of Business for photo of Paul Leonard., 2007 March 1; 99.0 MB 177
    - Business: Photo Session on May 7th from 1-4 in the Standish Room. Event is retirement reception for Paul Morgan, Sr., 2007 April 25; 65.6 MB 147
    - Business: Photo Session on May 7th from 1-4 in the Standish Room. Event is retirement reception for Paul Morgan, Sr., 2007 April 25; 65.6 MB 147
    - President's Office: 4/26/07 @ 3 - 5 PM Life Science RB (D'Ambra Auditorium) for UAlbany Organization of Women Faculty Open Forum with speaker Dr.Lisa Freehill. Pictures of her and also the participants before the talk and afterwards would be great., 2007 April 26; 47.9 MB 55
    - School of Business: 5/9/07 @ 12:30 - 1:30 PM Campus Center Ballroom for Awards Luncheon, 2007 May 10; 51.2 MB 114
    - School of Business: 5/16/07 @ 12 Noon, Fireside Lounge, Campus Center for the School of Business's annual class picture (Class of 2008). There will be 39 students in the picture., 2007 May 17; 19.4 MB 18
    - President's Office: 5/19 from 6 - 8 PM Standish Room, New Library for Honorary Degree Commencement Dinner Format: brief cocktail time and sit down dinner for ~ 60 (VIPs, O.I.C. & VP's along with other Commencement Platform Party members) w/ some short speeches by Honorary Degree recipients & Susan Herbst, 2007 May 20; 297.8 MB 74
    - School of Business: 5/19/07 from 11:30 - 12:30 at the Sefcu Arena for candid shots after Graduate Ceremony., 2007 May 20; 63.7 MB 121
    - School of Business:; 11:30 - 1:30 in Bus. Admin Bldg, room 219 on Aug. 24th. Pictures of new MBA and Accounting students., 2007 August 14; 845.9 MB 276
    - School of Business: Photos of student athletes at the main entrance of the SEFCU Arena on 8/27/07 from 1:00 - 2:30 p.m., 2007 September 5; 68.4 MB 171
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: Move-in day photos to include general shots of students moving in, a male and female student laden down with belongings, different ethnicities, Susan Herbt helping out, parents hugging their child, etc. Also, photos of check presentation from Holiday Inn at 10:45 a.m. at State Quad on the steps or under a canopy if rain., 2007 September 5; 176.5 MB 179
    - School of Business: 10/25/07 from 6 - 8 p.m. at the capitol region Alumni Event located in the UHALL atrium., 2007 September 25; 72.9 MB 128
    - School of Business: 1/25/08 @ 11 AM - 12:30 PM, BA 313A for group photo and individual head shots., 2008 January 25; 43.4 MB 125
    - School of Business: Photo session: 5/7/08 in NanoFab North for the Research Forum from 5:30 - 7:30 pm., 2008 May 7; 348.4 MB 177
    - School of Business: Photo session: 5/7/08 in NanoFab North for the Research Forum from 5:30 - 7:30 pm., 2008 May 7; 348.4 MB 177
    - School of Business: Photo session: 5/9/08 @ 11 a.m. for a Blue Ribbon Panel of CIO's event at the School of Business., 2008 May 9; 40.7 MB 56
    - School of Business: 5/14/08 @ 1:30 PM in Campus Center Assembly Hall for class picture of 30 MBA students., 2008 May 14; 6.9 MB 3
    - SOB_Beer Distribution Game, 2008 August 22; 33.4 MB 84
    - Accounting Orientation, 2008 August 26; 67.1 MB 119
    - SOB_future building site ceremony, 2008 October 3; 79.0 MB 102
    - Women's MBA, 2009 March 11; 194.1 MB 224
    - School of Business Erns t& Young Check Presentation, 2009 May 1; 8.5 MB 14
    - Evening MBA Research Forum, 2009 May 7; 54.6 MB 123
    - School of Business Awards, 2009 May 7; 74.8 MB 191
    - MBA, 2009 May 14; 71.0 MB 27
    - SOB Grad Commencement Reception, 2009 May 17; 53.3 MB 81
    - Dr. Vladimir Sokolov_SoB, 2009 July 22; 35.0 MB 60
    - SOB_Grad Orientation, 2009 August 28; 723.4 MB 194
    - Ernst and Young Alumni Check Presentation, 2010 April 29; 8.7 MB 11
    - SoB and alumn, 2010 May 5; 6.1 MB 18
    - SoB_Awards Luncheon, 2010 May 5; 46.8 MB 110
    - Evening MBA Research Forum, 2010 May 5; 61.6 MB 129
    - SoB_Architectural Design Unveiling, 2010 May 10; 78.6 MB 184
    - Go Green MBA, 2010 May 12; 14.2 MB 12
    - SoB_commencement, 2010 May 15; 36.9 MB 30
  - School of Social Welfare, 2013 October 29-2013 October 29; 1.11; 40
    - Social Welfare: 10/21/02 @ 11:45 AM Times Union Bldg. Wolf Rd. Albany check presentation digital, 2002 November 1; 73.2 MB 44
    - Social Welfare: 5/1/03 @ 11 AM Rockwell Center 421 W. Columbia St. Cohoes, NY Action photo: Students Toni Marion and Melissa Mosley with clients digital, 2003 April 29; 23.6 MB 55
    - Social Welfare: photo shoot: 6/9/03 @ 10:30 PM Milne 200 Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 23; 21.4 MB 63
    - Social Welfare: photo shoot: 6/9/03 @ 10:30 PM Milne 200 Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 23; 21.4 MB 63
    - Social Welfare: 6/11/03 @ 9 AM Desmond Hotel Albany Aging Seminar w/ Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 25; 19.7 MB 65
    - Social Welfare: 6/11/03 @ 9 AM Desmond Hotel Albany Aging Seminar w/ Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 25; 19.7 MB 65
    - Social Welfare: 5/18/04 @ 12 Noon Milne 200 Community Forum: Place Based Philanthropy digital, 2004 June 1; 43.9 MB 28
    - Social Welfare: 5/18/04 @ 12 Noon Milne 200 Community Forum: Place Based Philanthropy digital, 2004 June 1; 43.9 MB 28
    - School of Social Welfare: 10/5/04 @ 11 AM Richardson 108 various faculty and classroom shots digital, 2004 October 14; 196.5 MB 127
    - Social Welfare: 11/13/04 @ 3PM - 7 PM Milne 200 Memorial for Bill Reid digital, 2004 November 15; 178.2 MB 126
    - Social Welfare: 11/19/04 @ 12 Noon Draper 147 various locations digital, 2004 November 29; 185.5 MB 127
    - Social Welfare: 11/19/04 @ 3 PM Daughters of Sarah Nursing Facility Washington Ave Ext Student volunteers/interns digital, 2004 December 2; 88.3 MB 53
    - Social Welfare: 11/19/04 @ 2 PM Milne 200 Wesley Clark digital, 2004 December 6; 52.5 MB 39
    - Social Welfare: 12/9/04 @ 12:30 PM Westview Senior Ctr. Central Ave / Allen St. Students with senior clients digital, 2004 December 21; 289.1 MB 194
    - Social Welfare: 1/7/05 @ 10 AM Husted Offices/CTR for Excellence in Aging Services staff photo digital, 2005 January 18; 69.9 MB 50
    - President's Office: 1/5/05 @ 11:30 AM State Capital Bldg Rm 331/332 Sen. Bruno's office Presidents Kermit Hall and John Ryan with various legislators digital, 2005 January 18; 169.7 MB 117
    - Ctr. For Excellence in Aging Services: 2/9/05 @ 2:30 PM Downtown Campus TBA various group shots digital, 2005 February 14; 47.2 MB 28
    - Social Welfare: 9/02 @ Phillip Schuyler Middle School Albany, NY Time Dollar / Middle school kids and school supplies digital, 2005 February 22; 11.2 MB 18
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; 29.5 MB 12
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; 29.5 MB 12
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; 29.5 MB 12
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; 29.5 MB 12
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; 29.5 MB 12
    - Social Welfare: 4/6/05 @ 9 AM Richardson 209 Tara Nickle with Phil McCallion digital, 2005 April 5; 48.6 MB 35
    - Media and Marketing: 3/23/05 variours times Main Campus President for a Day: Cat Provost digital, 2005 April 6; 27.9 MB 17
    - Social Welfare: 5/14/05 between 2:30 and 3 PM SSW Faculty group portrait digital, 2005 May 5; 18.6 MB 12
    - Social Welfare: 7/27/05 @ 1:30 PM Draper 116 Social Work Education Consortium digital, 2005 August 3; 131.7 MB 93
    - Social Welfare: 11/2/05 @ 2:30 PM Page Hall Lounge Pres Hall w/ SSW faculty digital, 2005 October 27; 86.5 MB 62
    - Ctr for Excellence in Aging: 11/14/05 @ 8:30 AM - 10:00 AM Empire State Plaza Albany, NY Press Event: Medicare Part D Coverage digital, 2005 November 10; 634.6 MB 126
    - Social Welfare: 2/1/06 @ 4 - 6 PM Milne 200 Unveiling Ceremony / Distinguished Professor and Colllins Fellows digital, 2005 November 30; 428.5 MB 81
    - Social Welfare: 3/28/06 @ 3 PM - 5 PM CC Ballroom Town Meeting w/ Richard Catallano, 2006 April 4; 87.4 MB 50
    - School of Social Welfare: 12/13/06 @ 10:30 AM-12 Noon in the Legislative Office Building, Room 711 for Announcement of state funding from the Governor, NYS Senate and NYS Assembly for the SSW's Elder Network of the Capital Region (ENCR), 2006 December 14; 73.3 MB 88
    - School of Social Welfare: 5/19/07 @ 2:45 PM, outside in front of Page Hall, for photo of two new faculty members: Cathy Lewandowski and Heather Larkin., 2007 May 21; 37.1 MB 31
    - School of Social Welfare: 5/23/07 @ 9:30 - 10:30 am, Life Sciences building 2nd floor auditorium for Diversity Conference Opening Remarks - types of shots: Susan Herbst, main speakers and introductions, as well as some general group shots. Point of contact: Pam 5/23/07 @ 12:45 - 1:45 pm, Life Sciences building 2nd floor auditorium for plenary session of Diversity Conference, 2007 May 24; 89.6 MB 124
- Administration, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; 2; 970
  - Administration, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; 2.1; 970
    - Provost's Office: 5/24/01 @ 3 PM New Library / Standish Room Agreement signing w/ Kang Won Nat'l Univ (Korean) digital, 2001 June 7; 85.1 MB 74
    - Media and Marketing: 1/16/02 @ 2 PM President's Conference Rm UAB 427 IFW Meeting - presentation of new leadership digital, 2002 January 24; 75.9 MB 30
    - Provost's Office: 5/6/02 @ 11 AM Provost's Office UAB-401 Chancellor Awardees (students) color print, 2002 May 15; 21.5 MB 19
    - Outreach: 12/23/02 @ 2 PM 55 Colvin Ave. Albany Carlos Santiago and Carlos Schmidt digital, 2003 January 6; 227.2 MB 87
    - Media and Marketing: 6/17/03 @ 1 PM Nano Tech Center / Auditorium SUNY Board of Trustees Mtg. Digital, 2003 June 30; 31.7 MB 101
    - Advancement: 10/27/03 @ 10 AM Pres Office Barry, Bette and LaDuke; Bob Fortune presenting check digital, 2003 October 29; 17.5 MB 12
    - Advancement: 10/27/03 @ 10 AM Pres Office Barry, Bette and LaDuke; Bob Fortune presenting check digital, 2003 October 29; 17.5 MB 12
    - Media and Marketing: 10/28/03 @ 3 PM CC Ballroom President's Address to Faculty digital, 2003 October 30; 374.0 MB 61
    - Media and Marketing: 2/2/04 @ 12 noon CC Ballroom Announcement w/ Carlos Santiago digital, 2004 February 16; 34.6 MB 23
    - Media and Marketing: 2/2/04 @ 12 noon CC Ballroom Announcement w/ Carlos Santiago digital, 2004 February 16; 34.6 MB 23
    - Planned Giving: 4/28/04 @ 9:30 AM Advancement Office UAB Planned Giving Staff Photo digital, 2004 May 10; 34.3 MB 23
    - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 @ Noon CC Executive Committee having lunch with students digital, 2005 May 11; 41.2 MB 23
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 3 PM Pres. Office Mtg w/ Sen. Hugh Farley digital, 2005 September 26; 30.6 MB 24
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 3:30 PM CC Assembly Hall Senate Meeting digital, 2005 September 26; 46.1 MB 31
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 10:30 AM President's Office Athletic Master Plan Mtg w/ Lee McElroy digital, 2005 September 26; 24.3 MB 17
    - President: 12/12/05 @ 10 AM Alumni House UAS Board of Directors Meeting - Check Presentation digital, 2005 December 15; 178.7 MB 28
    - President: 12/15/05 @ 9:30 AM Standish Room Mission Review w/ SUNY System Administration, 2005 December 15; 123.9 MB 24
    - President: 12/12/05 @ 6:30 PM Standish Room Business Higher Education Roundtable (BHER) Dinner, 2005 December 15; 409.4 MB 144
    - President: 4/27/06 @ 4 PM UAB 437 University Council Meeting, 2006 May 11; 100.3 MB 47
    - President: 4/27/06 @ 4 PM UAB 437 University Council Meeting, 2006 May 11; 101.9 MB 48
    - Government Relations: 2/27/07 @ 8 a.m. - 4 p.m. Legislative Office Building and State Capitol for SUNY Day. Schedule and types of shots are forthcoming., 2007 February 28; 23.6 MB 50
    - Planned Giving: 5/4/07 @ 10:30 AM Campus Center in front of the small fountain for photo of Student Award winners, 2007 May 4; 13.2 MB 22
    - Planned Giving: 5/31/07 @ 11:30 AM President's Office UNH for photo of Ted Andersan, Susan Herbst and others, 2007 May 31; 48.9 MB 58
    - Psycology Services: 6/13/07 @ 11 AM Pscyholog Services Center for new photos of doors, 2007 June 14; 253.1 MB 161
    - Media & Marketing: 1-2 pix of the 3 new directors for News in Photos and update Story for Enrollment Management, Latonia Spencer, Beth Post and Joel Davis on 9/28/07 from 8:30 - 9:30 a.m. in Student Services Center, Campus center B-25/26., 2007 October 11; 11.4 MB 20
    - Media & Marketing: 10/11/017 at 11:30 in UHALL atrium to take group shots and various shots of university president's from Afganistan. Then head over to Science Library to take shots near minerva., 2007 October 24; 23.9 MB 51
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/8/08 @ 9:45 a.m. at the University Library foyer with George Philip and Susan Phillips passing out coffee., 2008 May 8; 26.1 MB 56
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/8/08 @ 9:45 a.m. at the University Library foyer with George Philip and Susan Phillips passing out coffee., 2008 May 8; 26.1 MB 56
    - President's Office: Photo session: 5/8/08 @ 3:30 pm for The Valedictorian Celebration in the Patroon Room (CC), 2008 May 8; 33.2 MB 78
    - UPD Swearing_In, 2008 July 12; 11.8 MB 32
  - Presidents, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; 2.2; 786
    - Dr Robert J Jones, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; 2.2.1; 786
- Athletics, 2004 October 10-2016 April 22; 3; 3350
  - Athletics, 2004 October 10-2016 April 22; 3.1; 3350
    - University Relations: 1/31/01 @ 1:45 PM RACC Hall of Fame Room Surprise digital, 2001 February 12; 80.9 MB 57
    - Media and Marketing: 3/13/02 @ 2 PM RAAC press conf / Will Brown digital, 2002 March 27; 23.7 MB 19
    - Sports Information: Photo session: 5/6/02 @ 1 PM RACC Hall of Fame Room press conference: Trina Thomas-Peterson; new head women's basketball coach digital, 2002 May 20; 61.4 MB 52
    - Sports Information: 11/5/02 @ 2:30 PM RACC Arena Men's and Women's Basketball Team Photos digital, 2002 November 20; 205.6 MB 77
    - Sports Information: 11/6/03 @ 3:30 PM RACC Men's and Women's Basketball Team Photos digital, 2003 November 20; 67.6 MB 47
    - Media and Marketing: 1/21/04 @ 5:45 PAC B-28 Pep Band rehearsal digital, 2004 February 5; 96.4 MB 46
    - Media and Marketing: 1/21/04 @ 5:45 PAC B-28 Pep Band rehearsal digital, 2004 February 5; 96.4 MB 46
    - photo session: 2/7/04 @ 4 PM RACC Big Purple Growl, 2004 February 11; 524.1 MB 207
    - photo session: 2/7/04 @ 4 PM RACC Big Purple Growl, 2004 February 11; 524.1 MB 207
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; 53.9 MB 35
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; 145.1 MB 91
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; 145.1 MB 91
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; 53.9 MB 35
    - Media and Marketing: 8/5/04 @ 3:30 PM Football Practice Field ESPN broadcast w/ Mike Ditka and others digital, 2004 August 19; 77.4 MB 65
    - Media and Marketing: 8/5/04 @ 3:30 PM Football Practice Field ESPN broadcast w/ Mike Ditka and others digital, 2004 August 19; 77.4 MB 65
    - Media and Marketing: 8/17/04 @ 9:30 AM Giant's Practice Jody McDonald; broadcaster for WCDB digital, 2004 August 31; 20.8 MB 16
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 12:30 PM Soccer Field Women's Soccer Team Photo digital, 2004 August 31; 56.3 MB 22
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 9 AM Football Field President Ryan w/ Phil McConky digital, 2004 August 31; 51.3 MB 37
    - Media and Marketing: 8/17/04 @ 9:30 AM Giant's Practice Jody McDonald; broadcaster for WCDB digital, 2004 August 31; 20.8 MB 16
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 12:30 PM Soccer Field Women's Soccer Team Photo digital, 2004 August 31; 56.3 MB 22
    - Sports Information: 8/20/04 @ 9 AM various locations Team Photos: Women's Volleyball and Women's Field Hockey digital, 2004 September 3; 102.4 MB 51
    - Sports Information: 10/15/04 @ 6 PM RACC / Hall of Fame Room Hall of Fame Awards Dinner digital, 2004 October 4; 227.7 MB 154
    - Sports Information: 2/1/05 @ 3 PM PE Gym Women's Softball Team digital, 2005 February 11; 43.9 MB 22
    - Sports Informaiton: 5/2/05 @ 5:30 PM RACC Arena Annual Great Dane Awards digital, 2005 April 27; 235.6 MB 144
    - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President's Speech to Faculty digital, 2005 April 27; 142.6 MB 96
    - Media and Marketing: 4/18/05 @ Noon CC Pres Hall meets w/ Betty Capaldi (SUNY Administration) digital, 2005 May 2; 40.7 MB 22
    - Sports Information: 5/18/05 @ Noon Football field area Groundbreaking for Lacrosse fields digital, 2005 June 1; 255.6 MB 127
    - Sports Information: 5/18/05 @ Noon Football field area Groundbreaking for Lacrosse fields digital, 2005 June 1; 255.6 MB 127
    - Sports Information: 5/18/05 @ Noon Football field area Groundbreaking for Lacrosse fields digital, 2005 June 1; 255.6 MB 127
    - Sports Information: 8/17/05 @ 1 PM Football Bleachers various team photos for media guide digital, 2005 August 29; 239.2 MB 122
    - Sports Information: 9/7/05 @ 3:50 PM gym / soccer field headshots / team photo digital, 2005 September 20; 143.2 MB 91
    - Media and Marketing: 9/7/05 @ 8 AM President's Office Senate Higher Ed Team digital, 2005 September 20; 23.0 MB 17
    - Sports Information: 10/7/05 @ 6 PM Hall of Fame Room Hall of Fame Induction_05 digital, 2005 October 17; 329.2 MB 137
    - Media and Marketing: 10/13/05 @ 3 PM PE Gym Women's Volleyball / the Ashleys digital, 2005 October 27; 67.7 MB 24
    - University Development: 3/17/06 @ 1:30 PM Lacrosse Field New Lacrosse Field, 2006 March 31; 155.8 MB 70
    - Sports Information: 5/9/06 @ 2:30 PM Fallon Field Lacrosse team photo, 2006 May 23; 68.3 MB 29
    - Sports Information: 5/9/06 @ 2:30 PM Fallon Field Lacrosse team photo, 2006 May 23; 204.3 MB 33
    - Sports Information: 5/18/06 @ 9:15 AM Softball field Women's Softball Team, 2006 June 1; 80.4 MB 10
    - Sports Information: 8/16/06 @ 10:30 AM various locations / RACC team photos, 2006 August 17; 111.0 MB 54
    - Sports Information: 10/20/06 @ 6:30 PM RACC Hall of Fame / Reception and Dinner, 2006 October 20; 244.2 MB 144
    - Athletics: 11/1/06 @ 11:15 AM SEFCU announcement / ribbon cutting, 2006 November 1; 134.4 MB 64
    - Development: 11/30/06 @ 1 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, (in the training room) for photo of Ashlee Reed, 2006 November 30; 115.9 MB 60
    - Media & Marketing: 6/14/07 @ 5:30 pm University Field for Special Olympics Tailgate party with Lee McElroy 6/14/07 @ 7:30 pm University Field (SEFCU Arena if raining) for Special Olympics Opening Ceremony (see Greta/Karl for details)., 2007 June 14; 134.8 MB 239
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session; Giants Media Day Thurs. July 26 @ 11:30 a.m. behind Science Library Bldg., 2007 August 6; 61.1 MB 85
    - Athletics: team shots of men's soccer, womens soccer & field hockey @ 2 p.m. on 9/4/07 at field hockey turf field, 2007 September 12; 81.1 MB 38
    - Athletics:; volleyball team shot on 9/5/07 @ 3:45 p.m.inside the volleyball gym., 2007 September 12; 19.2 MB 9